<resources>
    <string name="app_name">recipes</string>
    <string name="recipe1">Iconic Plate: Bistecca alla Fiorentina</string>
    <string name="des1">Bistecca alla Fiorentina is the symbol of Florence’s gastronomic traditions.
        It is a dish that represents the identity of Tuscany, of Profumo del Chianti and of Dario Cechinni’s
        butcher shop.This incredibly unique dish is composed of a 7.5cm thick T-bone steak, that contains no
        added salt, oil or marinades, prior to grilling. Diners can season their serving of Bistecca alla
        Fiorentina with Profumo del Chianti, Dario’s signature herb salt blend and the finest extra-virgin
        olive oil on hand.</string>
    <string name="ing1">1 porterhouse, cut 3-4 inches thick \n
1 Tbsp olive oil, more for drizzling\n
coarse sea salt\n
chopped fresh herbs such as rosemary or sage</string>
    <string name="pro1"> 1.Heat a charcoal grill or set a gas grill to high. Brush steak with olive oil and herbs if using.\n

        2.Grill on hottest part of grill, for 5 mins. Flip the steak.
        Grill on the second side for 5 minutes. Flip the steak to grill edges 3-4 mins each.\n
        3.When the meat is done remove it from grill and let it rest for 5 minutes for the juices to settle.\n
        4.After resting, drizzle with olive oil and sea salt before serving.</string>

    <string name="recipe2">Strawberry custard creams</string>
    <string name="des2">Bake a strawberry version of classic custard creams.
        Crisp vanilla biscuits are filled with jam and a delicious strawberry and custard buttercream.</string>
    <string name="ing2">CALORIES 266KCALS \n
FAT 13.1G (8.2G SATURATED)\n
PROTEIN 1.6G\n
CARBOHYDRATES 35.2G (18.3G SUGARS)\n
FIBRE 0.6G\n
SALT 0.1G\n</string>
<string name="pro2">1.Hull the strawberries and purée.\n
        2.Put the ★ ingredients in a small pan, and mix it up well before starting to cook.
    If you want a really creamy, smooth texture, I recommend straining the mixture through a sieve at this stage.\n
        3.Cook over low heat while mixing constantly with a whisk. When it starts to thicken,
    the hardening process will progress very quickly, so keep mixing!
</string>
    <string name="recipe3">Almond blancmange with blackcurrant sauce</string>
    <string name="des3">Creamy almond blancmange with a tart blackcurrant sauce is a classic English dessert that
        will certainly bring feelings of nostalgia. An excellent way to use up a glut of homegrown fresh
        blackcurrants.</string>
    <string name="ing3">CALORIES 531KCALS \n
FAT 37G (11.7G SATURATED) \n PROTEIN 9.8G \n
CARBOHYDRATES 40.4G (39.4G SUGARS) \n
FIBRE 1.8G \n
SALT 0.1G \n</string>
    <string name="pro3">1.Lightly oil 6 x 100-120ml (or 1 x 600-700ml) jelly moulds and set aside.
        Put the almonds into a liquidiser with 4 tbsp cold water and the single cream,
        then blend to produce a thick, gruel-like mixture.\n
        2.Line a large sieve with a single piece of damp muslin. Spoon in a quarter of the mixture, gather up the edges and gradually squeeze out as much of the almond ‘milk’ as you can into a bowl.
        Discard the leftover nut paste and repeat with the remaining mixture. You should be left with 300ml almond milk.
        3.Soak the gelatine leaves in a small bowl of cold water for 5 minutes. Put 4 tbsp water into a small pan with the 125g
        caster sugar and a pinch of salt, then heat gently until the sugar has dissolved and the liquid is clear.
        Lift the soaked gelatine leaves out of the bowl, squeeze out the excess water, then stir the leaves into
        the sugar syrup until they have dissolved. Stir this mixture into the almond milk and leave to cool.
    </string>
    <string name="recipe4">Tex-Mex inspired cheeseburger</string>
    <string name="des4">Give homemade burgers a Tex-Mex twist in this easy recipe. Serve spicy beef patties
        (made using our ultimate beef burger recipe) with a zesty slaw, jalapeños and a rich cheese sauce.</string>
    <string name="ing4">½ portion delicious. ultimate beef burgers\n
Veg oil for brushing\n
2 tbsp fajita seasoning\n
½ small white cabbage, finely shredded\n
2 medium carrots, peeled and grated\n
1 bunch coriander, roughly chopped (about 30g)\n
1 small red onion, finely chopped\n
3 tbsp mayonnaise\n
Grated zest and juice 1 lime\n
4 burger buns, toasted\n
Tomato ketchup and pickled jalapeños to serve</string>
    <string name="pro4">1.For the cheese sauce, whisk together 250ml evaporated milk and the corn flour in a saucepan. Put over a medium heat and bring it to the boil (whisking all the time), then simmer for 3 minutes. Remove from the heat and stir in the cheese, chilli powder, garlic and onion powders, and a pinch of salt. If the cheese isn’t fully melted, gently warm over a low heat until silky smooth. Adjust the thickness with a little more evaporated milk if needed. Keep warm until ready to serve.\n
    2.Heat a ridged griddle pan, heavy-bottomed frying pan or prepare a barbecue for high direct heat. Brush the burgers with oil and sprinkle with the fajita seasoning. Cook for 6-8 minutes until cooked through and well browned.\n
    3.While the burgers are cooking, toss together the cabbage, carrot, coriander, onion, mayo and lime zest and juice in a bowl. Season with salt and a little pepper.\n
    </string>

</resources>